Hello, and welcome to our sample movie.
This is a demonstration of the SRT subtitle format,
which is widely used for video subtitling.
SRT files contain numbered subtitle sequences
with start and end timestamps.
Each subtitle can span multiple lines
and includes timing information.
The format is: sequence number,
followed by the time range,
followed by the subtitle text.
Timestamps are in the format:
hours:minutes:seconds,milliseconds
SRT files are plain text and can be
created or edited with any text editor.
They're compatible with most video players
and video editing software.
You can include formatting like bold,
italic, or underlined text.
Thank you for viewing this sample SRT file!